one of the biggest challenges most typo
decks face is wanting to destroy all of
your opponent's creatures without
destroying your own unless you give all
of your creatures indestructible first
which is not completely out of the
question playing classic board wipes
like wrath of God damnation or
Blasphemous act just isn't going to cut
it but thanks to my friends at Wizards
of the Coast I've been given a special
preview card for Commander Masters that
hasn't seen a single reprint since its
launch back in Commander 2017 six years
ago let's check out
Kindred dominance
Kindred dominance is a seven Mana
sorcery that says choose a creature type
destroy all creatures that aren't of the
chosen type
that's right Kindred dominance is
effectively a one-sided board wipe
golgari elves rakdos goblins vampires
five colored dragons grix's Wizards
demere zombies and Ethan wraith typo all
of these typo decks can make full use of
this card at seven Mana this is quite a
costly card but when you cast this spell
you're probably going to win the game as
you'll likely be clearing the way for a
lethal swing what decks are you looking
forward to putting Kindred dominance in
also don't forget this is the first time
Kindred dominance has ever been printed
in foil and you can look to grab one
when Commander Masters releases on
August 4th
if you would like to learn more about
Commander Masters check out the link
below
thanks again to Wizards of the Coast for
this awesome preview
foreign